[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Social cognition is the cognitive processes that influence",
    "options": [
      "social schema",
      "social behavior",
      "social media",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Smooth and adaptive social interactions depend on the recruitment of",
    "options": [
      "perception",
      "attention",
      "language",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following abilities does not come under social cognition?",
    "options": [
      "rote memory",
      "face processing",
      "joint attention",
      "moral reasoning"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Social cognition develops primarily in old age.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "A theory of mind refers to a person's ability to understand and think about the __________ of other people.",
    "options": [
      "biological states",
      "mental states",
      "physical traits",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The __________ theory details the processes of observational learning and modeling, and the influence of self-efficacy on the production of behavior.",
    "options": [
      "behavioral",
      "socio-emotional",
      "social-cognitive",
      "cognitive-emotional"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "__________ processes account for the information that is selected for observation in the environment.",
    "options": [
      "motivational",
      "production",
      "retention",
      "attentional"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Children become more aggressive when they observe aggressive or violent models.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The __________ model of observational learning involves real or fictional characters displaying behaviors in books, films, television programs, or online media.",
    "options": [
      "symbolic",
      "live",
      "verbal instructional",
      "contextual"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "__________ refers to the anticipated consequences of a person's behavior.",
    "options": [
      "self-efficacy",
      "expectations",
      "intrinsic reinforcement",
      "extrinsic reinforcement"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  }
]